Viewers all over the world, be ready to begin to count your blessings after the prayer.
Whatever challenges you are facing, Jesus - with Him, all things are possible.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
For those on the sick bed, that is not where you belong.
Affliction in your blood are things of the past, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Anywhere in your organs - be free, in the name of Jesus!
I can hear you being free, in the name of Jesus!
That affliction is a thing of the past, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Healing hands of Jesus are on you, in the name of Jesus!
Holy Ghost!
Begin to feel the freedom right now!
Begin to feel the healing!
Begin to feel that freedom in your bones, blood, kidney, liver!
Freedom!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Jesus says, "It's over!"
That sickness is over!
That affliction is over!
That disease is over!
That limitation is over!
That setback is over!
That failure is over!
Limitation is over!
Stagnation is over, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I want to hear from you - it is over!
Mean it - it is over!
From your heart - it is over!
Say it from your heart - it is over, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, open your lips. Share your testimony to those who care to listen.
Hallelujah! What the Lord has done for you, you cannot tell it all.
Hallelujah!
When Jesus says you are healed, you are healed!
When Jesus says you are saved, you are saved!
When Jesus says you are blessed, you are blessed!
Jesus is not a man that lies.
You are free, in the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Why are you rejoicing?
Because it is over!
TT: Unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 09/09/2018